Guide to the Internation Brotherhood of Teamsters Communications Department records, 1958-1983 IBT0005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Communications Department records
1958-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0005
31 Linear Feet
This collections contains the records of the Internation Brotherhood of Teamsters Communications Department dating from 1958-1983. Included are publications distibuted by the department dating from 1977-1983 and minutes of the General Executive Board from 1958-1959.
Arrangement
Organized into two series: Publications and Newspaper Clippings; Publications are further divided into two subseries, Teamsters Division Publications and Teamsters Division Pamplets and Printed Materials.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by IBT Communications Department, May 10, 2010 [2010.070]
Scope and Contents
This collections contains the records of the Internation Brotherhood of Teamsters Communications Department dating from 1958-2011. Included are publications distibuted by the department dating from 1963-2011 and minutes of the General Executive Board from 1957-1958.
Biographical / Historical
The Communications Department works closely with International Union departments, divisions, and affiliates to spread information on union programs and goals to members, their families, retirees, allied organizations, public officials, the news media, and the general public. The department also promotes Teamsters concerns and campaigns to the news media, and responds to media inquiries.
Labor; Publications; Labor unions
- Publications, 1963-2011; ibt0005 Series 1; 1 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by publication, then chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains publications distributed by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Communications Department.
  The monthly publication of the Communications Department was the Teamsters News Service which was distributed throughout the organization with the purpose of informing other Teamsters publications about important events or announcements. Common features would include collections of relevant political cartoons and tips for IBT publication editors. This collection also includes pamphlets, handouts, and other English, French, and Spanish-language materials developed by the Teamsters Communication Department.
  - Teamsters Division Publications, August 2008 - April 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1; 0.5 Linear Feet
    - ABF Freight News, March 2010-November 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Airline News, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Airline TAMC-Nuts and Bolts News, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Bakery and Laundry News, April 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Brewery & Softdrink, May 2009-April 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Building and Construction Trades News, Winter 2006; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Carhaul News, April 2009-December 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Construction Trade, June 2009-April 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dairy News, February 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Division Newsletters-Airline News, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Freight News, April 2009-April 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Human Rights Commission, July 2009-April 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Industrial Trades, April 2008-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Leader, 1995-1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Leader, September 2000-January 2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Leader, April 2003-July 2006; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Leader, June 2006-December 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Leader, April 2008-July 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Leader, February 2009 -December 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Leader, March 2010-October 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Leader, March 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Motion Picture News, May 2009-December 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper, May 2009-April 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Public Services, September 2008-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Retirees News, April 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Spokesman, 2009-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Spokesman, 2010-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Tankhaul News, October 2008-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - The Teamsters' Organizing Campaign in the Communications Industry, December 1, 1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters Retiree Club Flyer, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Trade Show, April 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - UPS Teamster Update, July 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Women's News, August 2008-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Warehouse News, October 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Warehouse/U.S. Foodservice News, May 2009-October 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Waste and Recycling News, June 2009-April 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Teamsters Division Pamplets and Printed Materials, 1992-2008; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - America's Middle Class is Falling Apart 'America Needs the Employee Free Choice Act' Flyer/Call Script, ND; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Bakery and Laundry, 2000-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Brewery and Soft-Drinks, 1997-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Building Materials and Construction, October 2000-September 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Carhaul, January 1994-January 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Carhaul, November 2009; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Communications Kit, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Dairy, 2000-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Drive for America/U-Turn, 1995-2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Division Newsletters-Airline TAMC Nuts & Bolts News, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Drive-Up, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Education, Training, and Development, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Food Processing, 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Food Processing, 2003-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Freight, 1993-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Freight, 1999-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Florida Department of Corrections, 2012; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - GCIU, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Government Affairs, 1992-2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Human Rights Commission, 1996-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Industrial Trades, 1996-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - International Labor Hall of Fame, January, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - International Union Initiatives, 1994-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Law Enforcement League, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Leader, 1995-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Leader, September 2000-January 2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Leader, April 2003-July 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Leader, June 2006-December 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Miscellanous, 2008-2009; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Teamsters Publications, Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Motion Picture, 2001-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper, 2000-2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Organizing for Power, 1994-2005; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Parcel, 1996-2009; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Parcel-UPS News, 1993-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Parcel-UPS News, 1997-2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Parcel-UPS News, 2002-2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Pensions, 2005-2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Port, 2000-2005; Series Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Public Employee, 1997-2005; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Rail Conference, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Retiree News, 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Safety and Health, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Scholarships, 1994-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Scholarship-James R. Hoffa, 2000-2011; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Solid Waste, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Solid Waste-Reports, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Strategic Campaign Materials, 1994-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters Canada - Harassment in the Workplace Pamphlets, ND; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Teamster Canada - What is a Union? Your Teamsters Guide, ND; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters Directory, International Departments, Trade Divisions, Trade Conferences, ND; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Trade Show, 1994-2009; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Training and Development, 2009-2010; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Tankhaul, 1995-2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - La Voz, 1996-2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Warehouse, 1994-2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Warehouse News, 1995-2005; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Women's Conference, 2009-2010; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Women's News, 2005-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters News Service, Series 1 Suberies 3
    - Teamsters News Service, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters News Service, 27 December 1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Teamsters News Service, 17 January 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters News Service, 31 January 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters News Service, 14 February 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Teamsters News Service, 28 February 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Teamsters News Service, March 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters News Service, 3 March 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Teamsters News Service, 13 March 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Teamsters News Service, 25 March 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Teamsters News Service, 27 March 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Teamsters News Service, April 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Teamsters News Service, 10 April 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Teamsters News Service, 16 April 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Teamsters News Service, 23 April 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters News Service, 24 April 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters News Service, 6 May 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Teamsters News Service, 8 May 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters News Service, 22 May 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1 June 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Teamsters News Service, 12 June 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Teamsters News Service, 26 June 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Teamsters News Service, 17 July 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Teamsters News Service, 31 July 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Teamsters News Service, 14 August 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Teamsters News Service, 28 August 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Teamsters News Service, 11 September 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Teamsters News Service, 25 September 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Teamsters News Service, 9 October 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Teamsters News Service, November 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Teamsters News Service, 6 November 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Teamsters News Service, 16 November 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Teamsters News Service, 20 November 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Teamsters News Service, 11 December 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Teamsters News Service, 30 December 1964; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1977 March; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1977 May; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1978 April; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1978 May; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1978 June; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1978 August; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1978 September; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1978 October; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1978 November; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1978 December; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 January; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 February; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 March; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 April; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 May; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 June; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 July; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 August; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 September; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 October; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 November; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1979 December; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 January; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 February; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 March; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 April; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 May; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 June; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 July; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 August; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 September; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 October; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 November; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1980 December; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1981 June; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1981 August; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1981 September; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1981 October; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1981 December; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1981 January; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 February; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 March; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 April; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 May; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 July; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 August; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 September; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 October; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 November; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1982 December; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1983 January; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1983 March; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1983 April; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1987 May; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Teamsters News Service, 1987 July; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Teamsters News Service, The Nation, "Anything to Get Hoffa", 1967; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters news Service, Thomas Flynn Biography, July 1, 1971; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Teamster News Service Biographies, June 14, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      General
      Biographies of: M. E. 'Andy' Anderson, Jesse L. Carr, Edward M. Lawson, Weldon L. Mathis, Frank J. Matula JR., William J. McCarthy, George E. Mock, Joseph W. Morgan, Edward Nangle, Louis F. Peick, Salvatore ' Sam Provenzano, Ray Schoessling, Maurice R. Schurr, Joseph Trerotola, Arnie Weinmeister, Roy L. Williams
    - Teamsters News Service, Statement by Teamster General President Frank E. Fitzsimmons, August 1, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Teamster News Service Biographies, June 1, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Biographies of: M. E. Anderson, Jesse L. Carr, T. R. Cozza, Edward M. Lawson, Weldon L. Mathis, Frank J. Matula, William J. McCarthy, George E. Mock, Joseph W. Morgan, Louis F. Peick, Donald Peters, Jackie Presser, Salvatore 'Sam' Provenzano, Ray Schoessling, Maurice R. Schurr, Joseph Trerotola, Arnie Weinmeister, Roy L. Williams
    - Teamsters News Service, Teamster Historical Notes, August 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Drive Reporter, Vol. VI, No. 8, April 30, 1965; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 77 and S. 256, July 28, 1965; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Pamphlets: "Three Moral Arguments for Repeal of 14(b), "Right-to-Work" Law", "A Look at the Facts on Right-to-Work Laws", ND; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 1)
  - PriceCostco Teamsters Update, 23 October 1997; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Rail Teamster, Summer 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Rail Teamster, Winter 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - "Right-to-Work Laws and the Common Good" by the Rev. Jerome L. Toner, 1963; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Reprint from The International Teamster "States with Right-to-Work Laws", April 1963; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Reprint from The International Teamster "Repeal of 14(b) Labor's Number One Goal" Articles about 14(b), January-March 1965; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Reprint from The International Teamster "14(b) The Hoax of Compulsory Open Stop Divides America", June 1965; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Reprint from The international Teamster "The Air-Conditioned Sweatshop" Bill Kovach, December 1965; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Reprint from the International Teamster "Employees Use 'Right-to-Work' Laws as License to Swindle Workers" T.H. Vincent, February 1966; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Statement before select subcommittee on labor United States House of Representatives Statement by Sidney Zagri, Legislative Counsel, IBT, May 26, 1965; Series 1 (Box Box 31, Folder 6)
  - A Study of the Relationships Among Fatigue, Hours of Service and Safety of Operations of Trucks and Bus Drivers, 1972; IBT 0005 Series 1 (Box Shared Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Airline News, 2000-2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Teamster's Airline Journal, Fall 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Teamsters Bakery and Laundry, 2000-2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Biography, Joseph W. Morgan, May 1986; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Teamster Brewery and Soft Drink, Fall-Spring 2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters Building Material, 2000-2002; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Teamsters Carhaul Contract, 1999-2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Teamster Dairy News, 2000-2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters Drive News, February 1998; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Teamsters Food Processing News, 1995-2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Teamsters Freight Bulletin, 1997-2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Teamster Industrial Trade News, 2000-2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - The Teamster Leader, 1999-2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Teamster Motion Picture News, Winter - Spring 2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Teamsters National Costco News, Fall 2002; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters National Parking Council, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Newspaper Division, March 2000; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Newspaper, Magazine and Electronic Media Workers, Spring 2001 - Fall 2001; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Teamster Organizer, Spring 1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Teamsters Port News, 2000-2001; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters Public Employee News, 1995-2001; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters Tankhaul News, 1995-2001; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Teamsters UPS News, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Teamsters UPS Update, 1996-1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - The Teamster Warehouse News, 1996-2001; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Teamsters Women's News, 2000-2001; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - La voz de los Teamsters, 2001; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Teamster, July/August 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Teamster, September/October 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Teamster, January/February 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Teamster, March/April 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Teamster, May/June 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Teamster, July/August 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Teamster, November/December 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Teamster, January/February 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Teamster, March/April 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - UPS Teamster, Fall 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - UPS Teamster, Winter 2008-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Newspaper Clippings, ibt0005 Series 2; This series consists of copies of newspaper articles drawn from local newspaper in the U.S. and Canada, 1996-2003. The clippings are organized by date and the set of clippings for each date is indexed and the IBT locals that they deal with are highlighted on the indexpage.
  - "It Gets Dark Every Night: a reporters impressions of the mysterious search for Hoffa" by Jerry Stanecki, December 1975; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Karin Jones, Collection of Newspaper Clippings, 1955-1976; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1995 October 2 - 1995 October 13; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1995 October; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1995 November; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1995 November; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1995 December; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1995 December; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1995 December; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 January; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 January; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)